<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EBUZZ</string>
    <string name="sultan">Cast:"\n"Salman Khan, Anushka Sharma, Randeep Hooda, Amit Sadh"\n"Director:"\n"Ali Abbas Zafar"\n"Plot:"\n" A middle-aged wrestling champion (Salman Khan) tries to make a comeback to represent India at the Olympics.</string>
    <string name="Sing">Director:"\n" John Carney"\n"Writer: John Carney"\n"Stars: "\n"Ferdia Walsh-Peelo, Aidan Gillen, Maria Doyle Kennedy"\n"Plot:"\n"A boy growing up in Dublin during the 1980s escapes his strained family life by starting a band to impress the mysterious girl he likes.</string>
    <string name="Legend">Director: "\n"David Yates"\n"Writers:"\n" Adam Cozad (screenplay), Craig Brewer (screenplay)"\n"Stars: "\n"Alexander Skarsgård, Rory J. Saper, Christian Stevens"\n"PLot:"\n"arzan, having acclimated to life in London, is called back to his former home in the jungle to investigate the activities at a mining encampment. </string>
    <string name="Maardari">Director:"\n" Nishikant Kamat"\n"Writers:"\n" Shailja Kejriwal (story), Ritesh Shah (screenplay)"\n"Stars:"\n" Irrfan Khan, Jimmy Shergill, Vishesh Bansal"\n"A man named Nirmal loses his family in a man-made disaster, he starts the journey of seeking answers asking for accountability which urges him to take revenge.</string>
    <string name="Akira">Cast"\n"
Sonakshi Sinha as Akira Sharma"\n"
Konkona Sen Sharma"\n"
Anurag Kashyap"\n"
Amit Sadh"\n"
Raai Laxmi "\n"
Urmila Mahanta"\n"
Atul Kulkarni"\n"</string>
    <string name="rustom">Director: Dharmendra Suresh Desai"\n"
Writer: "\n"Vipul K. Rawal"\n"Stars: Akshay Kumar, Ileana, Arjan Bajwa"\n" Plot:"\n"Decorated officer. Devoted family man. Defending his honor. His name is RUSTOM.</string>
    <string name="Dishoom">Director:"\n" Rohit Dhawan"\n"Writers: "\n"Rohit Dhawan (story and screenplay), Tushar Hiranandani (story and screenplay) "\n"Stars: "\n"Nargis Fakhri, Akshay Kumar, Jacqueline Fernandez Plot:"\n"When India top batsman goes missing in the Middle East, two cops from either side of the Arabian Sea team up for a 36 hour manhunt</string>
</resources>
